Egmont Arens Papers
Egmont Arens Papers
- Industrial design records
  - Client and project file
    - Patent Attorneys, 1945; correspondence, handwritten notes (Box 21)
    - Patents: general information, 1937-1939; correspondence (Box 21)
    - Penney, J. C., Inc.
      - Monogram, sketches, photostats, paper samples, undated (Box 21)
      - Trademark, sketches, photostats, proofs, undated (Box 21)
    - Pet Milk Company, 1953; correspondence (Box 21)
    - Pfizer, Charles & Company, Inc., 1951; correspondence, proposal, report (Box 21)
    - Philip Morris, Inc.
      - Advertising ideas
        - Miscellaneous, 1947 (Box 21)
        - "Gentle Cigarette", 1955; letter, notes, clippings (Box 21)
        - "Lock Out the Aldehydes", ca. 1953 (Box 21)
        - "No Cigarette Hangover", undated; clippings (Box 21)
        - "Smoke Rings", correspondence, clippings, 1949; photo. ca. 1949 (Box 21)
      - Benson & Hedges, 1956; correspondence (Box 21)
      - Contracts, 1949-1956; correspondence (Box 21)
      - correspondence, 1947-1960; 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Dunhill Cigarettes, no
        - Notes, sample package, 1954 (Box 22)
        - Report by Color Research Institute of America, 1953 (Box 22)
      - Grocery store merchandising, 1948-1949; correspondence, handwritten notes (Box 22)
      - Interior Design
        - Louisville plant (Box 22)
          - Color specifications, reports, correspondence, photo., 1951-1952 (Box 22)
          - correspondence, 1951 (Box 22)
          - Miscellaneous, 1952 (Box 22)
          - Paint & fabric samples, undated (Box 22)
          - Photo., 35mm slides, ca. 1952 (Box 22)
          - Press releases & publicity, 1952 (Box 22)
          - Purchase order, correspondence, 1951 (Box 22)
          - Sketches, blueprints, floor plan, 1950-1951 (Box 22)
        - New York offices
          - correspondence, 1949-1957 (Box 22)
          - Floor plans, sketches, swatches, ca. 1950 (Box 22)
          - Notes, 1950; ca. 1956 (Box 22)
          - Publicity, 35 mm slides, photo., pr. mat., 1950 (Box 22)
        - Richmond plant
          - Color specifications, 1954 (Box 22)
          - correspondence, 1950-1956 (Box 23)
          - Floor plans, sketches, blueprints, photostats, photo., undated (Box 23)
          - handwritten notes, specifications, pr. mat., sketches, undated.; 1950-1951 (Box 23)
          - Main Street office entrance, correspondence, photo., blueprint, swatches, 1953-1956 (Box 23)
          - Stockton Street floor plan, sketches, handwritten notes, correspondence, swatches, 1953 (Box 23)
      - Market Research, correspondence, reports, sketches, 1948 (Box 23)
      - Marlboro Cigarettes
        - Advertising proofs, 1943 (Box 23)
        - Project X (Box 23)
        - correspondence, handwritten notes, sketches, 1953-1954 (Box 23)
        - Report, 1954 (Box 23)
        - Report on package & carton design by Color Research Institute of America, 1954 (Box 23)
      - Mayfield Cigarettes, 1959; correspondence, handwritten notes (Box 23)
      - Package of the Future, 1957; correspondence (Box 23)
      - Parliament Cigarettes
        - HiFi Filter, correspondence, notes, 1957 (Box 23)
        - New Package (Box 23)
        - Advertising proofs, photo., 1956 (Box 23)
        - correspondence, handwritten notes, pr. mat., 1954-1958 (Box 23)
        - Report on box designs by Color Research Institute of America, 1954 (Box 23)
      - Paul Jones Cigarettes, 1954; correspondence, notes (Box 24)
      - Phillip Morris Cigarettes
        - Christmas cartons, correspondence, 1956 (Box 24)
        - New package color, acetate sheets, sample packages, correspondence, 1957 (Box 24)
        - Project Mayfair (Box 24)
        - Clippings, 1955 (Box 24)
        - Photo., ca. 1955 (Box 24)
        - Photo captions, ca. 1955 (Box 24)
        - Presentations, paper samples, 1954 (Box 24)
        - Publicity, correspondence, 1955 (Box 24)
        - Reports, correspondence, handwritten notes, 1954-1956 (Box 24)
        - Report by Color Research Institute of America, paper samples, 1953-1954; 3 folders (Box 24)
        - Snap open carton, correspondence, handwritten notes, clippings, sample, 1954 (Box 24)
        - Vending machine inserts, 1957 (Box 24)
      - Polyethylene cigarette case, 1948; sketches, handwritten notes (Box 24)
      - Relative Visibility Survey, ca. 1955 (Box 24)
      - Revelation Pipe Tobacco, 1947; correspondence (Box 24)
      - Sales Meetings, 1948; correspondence, photo., speeches (Box 24)
      - Spud Cigarettes, 1947-1948; 1955; job outlines, correspondence, notes (Box 24)
      - Tobacco & Pipe Box, 1948; sketches (Box 24)
    - Photo-Color, ca. 1951; patent search (Box 24)
    - Photographic Paper, 1938; correspondence (Box 24)
    - Photometric Analysis, 1962; undated; letter, description of procedure (Box 24)
    - Plastic Boats, Inc. (Plastiboat)
      - Blueprints, handwritten notes, sketches, 1946 (Box 25)
      - Building instructions, undated (Box 25)
      - correspondence, 1946-1956 (Box 25)
      - Photographs
        - Prints, ca. 1946; 3 folders (Box 25)
        - Negatives, ca. 1946 (Box 25)
        - 35 mm slides, ca. 1946 (Box 25)
        - Publicity, copy, circulars, ca. 1946 (Box 25)
        - 12' Boat, photo., blueprints, handwritten notes, 1946-1948 (Box 25)
    - Plastic containers, 1943-1945; correspondence, photostats, sketch (Box 25)
    - Plastic Screen, undated; sketch (Box 25)
    - Plywood Structural Unit (Plyfold)
      - Claim for invention, 1942 (Box 25)
      - correspondence, 1941-1943 (Box 26)
      - Sketches, 1942 (Box 26)
    - [Alfred] Politz Research, Inc.
      - Chrysler Project, 1959-1960; report, correspondence, handwritten notes (Box 26)
    - Projection: Outdoor, undated; sketches, handwritten notes, photo (Box 26)
    - Projector, 1934; 1939; correspondence (Box 26)
    - Radar Corner Reflector, 1951; correspondence, claim for invention (Box 26)
    - Reflecto-Mount, 1952; 1961; correspondence, handwritten notes, sketches, photo-stats, paper samples (Box 26)
    - Refrigerator
      - correspondence, 1943-1949 (Box 26)
      - Design patent, patent application, photo., legal correspondence, 1943-1944 (Box 26)
      - Sketches, photostats, pr. mat., 1943 (Box 26)
    - Reynolds Metals Company
      - Aluminum furniture, correspondence, 1961 (Box 26)
      - Beer labels, samples, undated (Box 26)
      - Campbell Soup Company, 1941; correspondence (Box 26)
      - correspondence, 1941-1955; 2 folders (Box 26)
      - Glenmore Distilleries, 1941; correspondence, sketches (Box 26)
      - Goebel, Alfred, Inc., undated; frankfurter label, sketch (Box 26)
      - Grass, I.J. Noodle Company, 1941; correspondence (Box 26)
      - Lipton Tea, 1941; handwritten notes, sketch (Box 26)
      - Seeman Brothers, 1941; correspondence, sketches, photo., clipping (Box 26)
      - Silver Nip, 1941; sketches, letter (Box 26)
      - Stokely-Van Camp, 1941; correspondence, sketches (Box 26)
      - Swift & Company, 1941; correspondence, samples (Box 26)
      - Tropic Gold, undated; sketches, photo. (Box 26)
      - V-8 Juice, 1941; correspondence, sketch (Box 26)
      - Vick Chemical Company, 1941; correspondence (Box 26)
    - Riegel Paper Corporation, 1949-1950; correspondence, pamphlet (Box 26)
    - Roadway Housing Plan
      - correspondence, 1934; 1935,; 1944 (Box 27)
      - Presentation, 1935 (Box 27)
      - Sketches, handwritten notes, undated (Box 27)
    - Scale, Electric, 1943; sketch (Box 27)
    - Scoville Manufacturing Company, Garden Hose Line, 1956; correspondence, specifications (Box 27)
    - Scrambled Songs, Ins.
      - correspondence, 1951 (Box 27)
      - Ideas, handwritten & ts notes, 1951 (Box 27)
      - Incomplete drafts, ca. 1951 (Box 27)
      - Original words, ca. 1951 (Box 27)
      - Rough drafts, ca. 1951; 2 folders (Box 27)
      - Sample galleys, ca. 1951 (Box 27)
      - Song lists, ca. 1951 (Box 27)
    - Sebring Pottery Company, 1936; pottery design & marketing report (Box 27)
    - Sign: Illuminated, 1946; correspondence, patent application, photostats, patent copies (Box 27)
    - Slicing Machine, 1942-1943; correspondence, design, patent application, patent assignment, photostat (Box 27)
    - Soap: Protective Coating, Method of application, 1941; claim for invention (Box 27)
    - Society of the Plastics Industry, Badge Design, 1961; correspondence, sketches, blueprints (Box 27)
    - Socony Vacuum Oil Company, 1954; correspondence, sketches (Box 27)
    - Spinning Top, 1943-1944; correspondence,sketch (Box 27)
    - Steam Electric Products, Ltd. Steam Irons, 1950; correspondence, handwritten notes, sketches (Box 27)
    - Streamliner, 1946; correspondence (Box 27)
    - Switch Handle Lock, 1954-1955; correspondence, patent copies (Box 27)
    - Tank, 1942; sketches (Box 27)
    - Tappan Stove Company, 1948; correspondence (Box 27)
    - Tatham-Laird, Inc., 1952; 1954; correspondence (Box 27)
    - Tennessee Enamel Manufacturing Company, Coca-Cola Signs, 1945; undated; sketches, photostats (Box 27)
    - Tie Tree, 1937; correspondence (Box 27)
    - Trains of the Future, 1930-10; correspondence,notes, clippings, draft article, 36 (Box 27)
    - United Business Publishers Group, 1933; report (Box 28)
    - United States Economy Flow Chart, 1942; correspondence, charts, pr. mat. (Box 28)
    - United States Government, 1948-1956; correspondence (Box 28)
    - United States Patent Office, 1942-1944; bills, correspondence (Box 28)
    - United States Plywood, undated; report on plastic laminate market (Box 28)
    - Virginia Dare Extracts Company, 1940; clippings (Box 28)
    - Washing machine, 1943; letter, handwritten note (Box 28)
    - Waterman Pen Company, undated; sketches (Box 28)
    - Whitehall Pharmacal Company, Pill Dispenser, 1953; 1955; patent application, assignment, correspondence, pr. mat. (Box 28)
    - Whitewood Products Company
      - Lilliput Lumber
        - correspondence, 1935-1937 (Box 28)
        - Presentation, undated (Box 28)
        - Sketches, photostats, undated (Box 28)
        - Trademark registration, 1937 (Box 28)
    - Wigwam Mills, Inc., undated; pr. mat. (Box 28)
    - Wilbert Products, Inc., 1939; clippings (Box 28)
    - Wilson & Company, 1954; correspondence, handwritten notes. (Box 28)
    - World's Fair
      - Film: "Three-Thirds of a Nation"
        - correspondence, 1938 (Box 28)
        - correspondence, handwritten notes, 1939 (Box 28)
        - Magazines, 1939; 3 folders (Oversize 1)
        - Photo., pr. mat., 1939 (Box 28)
    - Wrigley's Gum
      - Posters, undated (Oversize 1)
  - General correspondence
    - 1931-1953, 12 folders (Box 29)
    - 1954-1966, undated, 12 folders (Box 30)
  - Office files
    - Billing recovery, 1958-1963 (Box 31)
    - Christmas cards
      - E.A. Business, 1939-1963 (Box 31)
      - From staff, 1950; 1951,; undated (Box 31)
    - Contract forms, undated (Box 31)
    - Job descriptions, 1945 (Box 31)
    - Letterheads, undated (Box 31)
    - Lists of staff & business friends, 1962; undated (Box 31)
    - Personal drawing account of Egmont Arens, 1951-1962 (Box 31)
    - Resumes, 1941-1963 (Box 31)
  - Photographs and slides
    - Prints & negatives
      - Advertising arts, 1931 (Box 32)
      - Advertising ideas, "Smoke Rings", 1931 (Box 32)
      - Anheuser-Busch, Inc., undated (Box 32)
      - Arens, Egmont, office of, undated (Box 32)
      - B. & K. and Kwick Chek Food Stores, undated (Box 32)
      - Boat, undated (Box 32)
      - Calking & Holden, Prize-winning Pictures Art Directors' Show, 1931 (Box 32)
      - Carborundum, undated (Box 32)
      - Chase Automobile, interior (negative), undated (Box 32)
      - Columbian Rope Company
        - Autoclave, undated (Box 32)
        - Chair, undated (Box 32)
      - Competitive Industrial Styling, undated (Box 32)
      - Designs by Egmont Arens, undated; 3 folders (Box 32)
      - Designs by Egmont Arens, undated; 4 folders (Box 33)
      - Exhibit: Dayton, Ohio, undated (Box 33)
      - "Fighting with Color", 1943 (Box 33)
      - Furniture designed by Egmont Arens, undated (Box 33)
      - The Great Atlantic & Pacific Tea Company
        - Bread products, 1943 (Box 33)
        - Coffee packages, 1930-1931; undated; 2 folders (Box 33)
        - Displays, 1931-1932; undated (Box 33)
      - Gynex, undated (Box 33)
      - Herreshoff Manufacturing Company, boat, 1945 (Box 34)
      - Hobart Brothers, Inc., mixer & slicer, 1937-1940; undated (Box 34)
      - Hoffman, bottle, 1930 (Box 34)
      - Hudnut, Richard, compact, perfume packages, 1931 (Box 34)
      - "Industrial Design Today" and exhibit, undated (Box 34)
      - International Paper Company, packages, 1931-1932; undated (Box 34)
      - Krasne Brothers, packages, undated (Box 34)
      - Matthew Products, Inc., packages, undated (Box 34)
      - Nashua Corporation, tape dispenser, undated (Box 34)
      - Negatives: Clients & others, 1936-1937; 1946,; 1949,; 1951,; undated; 17 rolls (Box 34)
      - Nestle-Lemur, hairdryer & waver, ca. 1939 (Box 35)
      - North Brothers, undated (Box 35)
      - Office Photographs, undated (Box 35)
      - Philip Morris, Inc., convention negatives, 1947; 15 rolls (Box 35)
      - Plastic Boats, Inc., undated (Box 35)
      - Plastic package for fruit, undated (Box 35)
      - Savory Toasters, undated (Box 35)
      - Seeman Brothers, Inc., undated (Box 35)
      - Society of Industrial Designers
        - 1947 Convention Dinner (Box 35)
        - 1949 Convention Dinner (Box 35)
      - Sweden House Bakers, undated (Box 35)
      - Toledo Scales, undated (Box 35)
      - Van Camp, cans, undated (Box 36)
      - Varityper, 1931 (Box 36)
      - Waterman Pens, 1931 (Box 36)
      - Wesson Oil & Snowdrift Sales Company, shortening can, undated (Box 36)
      - Wilbert Productions, Inc., truck, undated (Box 36)
      - World's Fair, 1939 (Box 36)
      - Unidentified, undated (Box 36)
    - 35 mm slides
      - Loose slides
        - A-Penn, undated (Box 37)
        - American Chicle Company, display stand, undated (Box 37)
        - Battleship, undated (Box 37)
        - Bristol-Myers Company, undated (Box 37)
        - Carborundum Company, 1948 (Box 37)
        - Crookes Laboratories, Inc, Enzo, California, undated (Box 37)
        - Designs of Egmont Arens, undated (Box 37)
        - Dif Corporation, undated (Box 37)
        - Dixon, Joseph Crucible Company, graphites, undated (Box 37)
        - "Fighting with Color", 1943 (Box 37)
        - Gerber Products Company, cereal baby food, undated (Box 37)
        - Glass dress, undated (Box 37)
        - Gobelin, 1948-1949 (Box 37)
        - Great Atlantic & Pacific Tea Company
          - Ann Page line, 1952 (Box 37)
          - Various brands, 1940-1948 (Box 37)
        - Higgins Ink Company, filigree brand, undated (Box 37)
        - Independent Grocer s Alliance, (I.G.A.) coffee & teas, undated (Box 37)
        - Italian Cook Salad Oil, undated (Box 37)
        - Jenkins Brothers
          - Gold Seal Friction Tape, 1948 (Box 37)
          - Jar rings, undated (Box 37)
        - Main of Orleans Sherry, undated (Box 37)
        - Major Treat Ice Cream, undated (Box 37)
        - Mars Candy, display, 1944 (Box 37)
        - Meador Peanut Brittle, 1946 (Box 37)
        - Mobile Air-Sea Base, 1942 (Box 37)
        - Monegal, NASA: Spanish dancer, undated (Box 37)
        - North Brothers, ice crusher-chopper, undated (Box 37)
        - Northern Electric Company, radios, undated (Box 37)
        - Old projects, 1948; undated (Box 37)
        - Packages, 1949; 1951,; undated (Box 37)
        - Red Cross and Seminole Towels, undated (Box 37)
        - Q.T. Pie Crust, undated (Box 37)
        - Reynolds Metals Company (Box 38)
        - Foil, undated (Box 38)
        - Metals & foil, undated (Box 38)
        - Rockwood & Company, chocolate products, undated (Box 38)
        - Sarong, undated (Box 38)
        - Seeman Brothers, Inc., White Rose Foods, undated (Box 38)
        - Seven Minute Pie Mix, undated (Box 38)
        - Six O'Clock Waffle Mix, undated (Box 38)
        - Sklar Manufacturing Company, 1945 (Box 38)
        - Swan Disposables, undated (Box 38)
        - Sweden House, undated (Box 38)
        - Thanx, undated (Box 38)
        - Virginia Dare Extract Company, undated (Box 38)
        - White House Milk, undated (Box 38)
        - Whitehall Laboratories, undated (Box 38)
        - Wilbert Floor Wax and Shoe Polish, 1949 (Box 38)
        - World's Fair, 1939 (Box 38)
      - Boxed slides
        - Slide box 1
          - Sections 1-8 Appetite Appeal, 1940-1949 (Box 39)
          - Sections 9-15 Color Cynamics, 1948-1956 (Box 39)
        - Slide box 2
          - Sections 1-11 Color Theory, 1947-1948 (Box 39)
          - Sections 12-15 Design Influences, 1948-1949 (Box 39)
        - Slide box 3
          - Sections 1-15 Package Design, studies, 1948-1949 (Box 40)
        - Slide box 4
          - Sections 1-7 Holsum Air Shots and others, 1956 (Box 40)
          - Sections 8-11 Holsum Bread, 1950 (Box 40)
          - Sections 12-15 Industrial Design, 1949 (Box 40)
        - Slide box 5
          - Sections 1-14 Merchandising, undated (Box 41)
        - Slide box 6
          - Sections 1-15 Miscellaneous, undated (Box 41)
    - Lantern slides
      - Arens Organization, undated; 3 folders (Box 42)
      - A.A. Armstrong, embossed linoleum, undated (Box 42)
      - Art line, undated; 2 folders (Box 42)
      - PO-A. Brodovitch-Athelia, undated (Box 42)
      - Packaging, undated (Box 42)
      - Packaging, 1937; undated; 3 folders (Box 43)
      - Plastic, undated; 2 folders (Box 43)
      - Streamlining in Nature, undated; 2 folders (Box 44)
      - Typography, 1932; undated; 3 folders (Box 44)
      - Typography, 1934; undated; 4 folders (Box 45)
  - Publicity file
    - Clippings about Egmont Arens, with scrapbook, 1936; re: Dayton Lecture (Box 46)
    - Material prepared by Egmont Arens Organization
      - Client captions, 1935-1946; undated (Box 46)
      - handwritten notes, layout, undated (Box 46)
      - Pr. mat., 1943; 1950,; undated (Box 46)
      - Proqrams, 1929-1949; undated (Box 46)
    - News releases, 1939-1954 (Box 46)
    - Promotional material, undated; 3 folders (Box 47)
    - Scrap book, undated (Box 47)
    - Scrap books (2), 1920-1936; undated (Package 2)
    - Testimonial letters, 1934-1958 (Box 47)
  - Writings
    - Arens, Egmont
      - Articles
        - "A & P Coffee", undated (Box 48)
        - "The Advertising Agency Enters Packaging", undated (Box 48)
        - "Automobiles Have It", undated (Box 48)
        - "Challenge", undated (Box 48)
        - "The Cigarette Package of the Future", undated (Box 48)
        - "Color Problems of the Architect", undated (Box 48)
        - "Commission to Design Caldwell Products Bottles & Labels", undated (Box 48)
        - "Cosmetic Displays", undated (Box 48)
        - "Design for Living", undated (Box 48)
        - "Designing the Royal Guest & Sunny Morn Coffee Packages", undated (Box 48)
        - Drafts of articles by Egmont Arens, undated (Box 48)
        - Ideas, handwritten notes, undated (Box 48)
        - "Egmont Arens Designs New Paraffine Companies Showroom", undated (Box 48)
        - "Engineered Styling New Trend", undated (Box 48)
        - "Five Ways to Lose Money on Your Packages", undated (Box 48)
        - "Follow-Through Wins the Game", undated (Box 48)
        - "Glass Packages: Consumer Engineered", undated (Box 48)
        - "Good or Bad Packages: How to Tell?", undated (Box 48)
        - "Heide Goes to Supermarket", undated (Box 48)
        - "History of the Redesigning of the Higgins Ink, Pastes & Mucilages", undated (Box 48)
        - "How a Fast-Selling Bread Wrapper Was Designed for Holsum Bakers", undated (Box 48)
        - "The How & Why of Creating a New Label for Decaf", undated (Box 48)
        - "How to Find Your Packaging P.Q.", undated (Box 48)
        - "How to Relate Package to Advertising in other Media", undated (Box 48)
        - "Imagination for Sale", undated (Box 48)
        - "It's Thrifty to Be Smart", undated (Box 48)
        - "Kent, Rockwell", undated (Box 48)
        - "Kitchen Design that Avoids Monotony", undated (Box 48)
        - "Low Pressure Molding of Carrying Cases", undated (Box 48)
        - "Make It Easy for The Prospect", undated (Box 48)
        - "Making Readers More Responsive to Advertising", undated (Box 48)
        - "Marching Out of Step Pays in Packaging", undated (Box 48)
        - "New Era in Boat Building", undated (Box 48)
        - "One Million Can't Be Wrong", undated (Box 48)
        - "Our Sublimated Fifth Sense", undated (Box 48)
        - "Packaging", undated (Box 48)
        - "Packaging for Mass Consumption", undated (Box 48)
        - "Packaging Standardization", undated (Box 48)
        - "Packaging Up", undated (Box 48)
        - "Photography", undated (Box 48)
        - "A Plea for Imagination", undated (Box 48)
        - "Program for a $2 Billion Market", undated (Box 48)
        - "Streamline as You Rebuild", undated (Box 48)
        - "Ten Outstanding Packages of Today", undated (Box 48)
        - "The Store of the Future", undated (Box 48)
        - "The Train of Tomorrow", undated (Box 48)
        - "We Acquire New Eyes", undated (Box 48)
        - "Package Engineering", 1930 (Box 48)
        - "Display Engineering", 1931 (Box 48)
        - "Color", 1932 (Box 48)
        - "Horton's Ice Cream Package", 1932 (Box 48)
        - "Super Suds & Ivory Snow Packages", 1932 (Box 48)
        - "Three Packaging Steps Necessary Essentials to Spontaneous Selling", 1932 (Box 48)
        - "Designing for the Chain Store", 1933 (Box 48)
        - "Package Takes Confusion Out of Product Demonstration", 1933 (Box 48)
        - "Second Annual Packaging Roundtable", 1934 (Box 48)
        - "Streamline for Recovery", 1934 (Box 48)
        - "How to Use Type on Your Packages", 1934 (Box 48)
        - "Packaging Marches On", 1935 (Box 48)
        - "Protection by Packaging", 1935 (Box 48)
        - "The Color Racket", 1935 (Box 48)
        - "Consumer Engineering vs. Consumer Research", 1935 (Box 48)
        - "Drug & Cosmetic Industry", 1935 (Box 48)
        - "Use Black to Sell Color", 1935 (Box 48)
        - "What Will They Buy Next Year", 1935 (Box 48)
        - "How I Produce a New Pack", 1935 (Box 48)
        - "New Packages Aid Sales, Cut Consumer Cost", 1936 (Box 48)
        - "Next Year's Cars", 1936 (Box 48)
        - "Streamline America", 1936 (Box 48)
        - "What Should the Designer Aim at in This Field", 1936 (Box 48)
        - "Where is Liquor Packaging Going?", 1936 (Box 49)
        - "Women's Hands Determine Sales", 1936 (Box 49)
        - "Best Design of the Month", 1937 (Box 49)
        - "Decorative Trends for 1937" (Box 49)
        - "Looking Over the Industrial Designer's Shoulder Memo valet", 1937 (Box 49)
        - "Packaging Pays", 1937 (Box 49)
        - "Photography in Business & Profession", 1937 (Box 49)
        - "What Makes Designs that Click", 1938 (Box 49)
        - "Packaging", 1938 (Box 49)
        - "Atlas Batteries", 1939 (Box 49)
        - "Eye Appeal for Transit Vehicles", 1939 (Box 49)
        - "How to Make Things Today that Will Sell Tomorrow", 1939 (Box 49)
        - "A Selling Tool Untried for Cigarettes", 1940 (Box 49)
        - "Good Design has no Recipe", 1940 (Box 49)
        - "Whither Styling?", 1940 (Box 49)
        - "Egmont Arens & Radio Today", 1940 (Box 49)
        - "New Trends in Coffee Today", 1940 (Box 49)
        - "Easy to Look at -- Easy to Use", 1940 (Box 49)
        - "Color Harmony Manual & Color Harmony Index", 1942 (Box 49)
        - "Color in the Factory", 1943 (Box 49)
        - "Fighting with Color Clippings", 1943 (Box 49)
        - "The Post-War Refrigerator", 1943 (Box 49)